What?
The deputy had an accident?
The assailant killed in the
shootout was indeed one of Burin’s men.
It's a good thing Vicky is in there,
otherwise I'd be worried.
Not only are you a great driver,
but you also have such strong determination.
I'm so proud of you.
My son just came back
from abroad earlier this year.
I'd like him to get to know your daughter.
If the two of them like each other.
That would be wonderful.
I never interfere in my child's private life.
Uh...
Congratulations on the top score.
You certainly lived up to
your reputation, Captain Tara.
How did you know?
Well
I'm your fan-club.
Hey.
I saw the news of Captain Tara's raid
at Pak Khlong.
- It was so cool.
- Really?
It was so cool.
- And then...
- 021
What are you doing here alone?
Why aren't you talking to the others, huh?
We're allowed to use our
real names and swap contacts now
Probably...
Nobody wants to get to know me.
I’m sorry for making you feel bad.
That was my mistake.
It’s totally fine.
Well,
you can’t
please everyone all the time.
There are bound to be things we don't like.
Hmm.
Your mindset has improved a lot.
But honestly, during
the training, I secretly admired you.
Wait,
What were you admiring?
Oh.
you criticized me so hard.
I wanted to run home on the very first day.
But you made it through everything,
didn't you?
You did a great job.
Yay!
It’s because I’ve had great encouragement.
That’s how I’ve made it this far.
And thank you for being so tough on me,
Instructor.
For making me realize that
I am...
Stronger than I ever thought I could be.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Uh-huh.
Hey.
Drinking like that will knock you out.
Hmm.
In other matters,
I might not be able to compete with anyone.
But when it comes to drinking,
I'm the most confident.
Cheers!
Bottoms up.
It’s already going to my head tonight.
That's not called being confident.
That's called being cocky.
Huh?
Then why didn't you stop me?
You were too busy talking."
So, you're not just cocky.
But you also like playing the victim.
Hey, careful.
See? Always playing the victim like this.
Foul
mouth.
But you're also cute.
Hey,
you're talking nonsense because you're drunk.
It's time for you to go to bed.
Go on.
I don't want to go back yet
Can we go to the beach?
Please.
We're leaving soon,
and haven't even gone for a swim yet.
Please.
Please. Please.
Umm.
Ok.
Go.
Hey.
You.
Wait.
We're here.
Hey.
The instructor said
we can use our real names now.
You’ve known my name since
the day I ordered that cake.
Umm.
But I haven't told you my name yet.
So tell me then.
But if you don't want to know,
I don't have to tell you.
Of course I want to know.
Come on, tell me already.
I'm Vicky.
My real name is Phavika.
That's a very beautiful name.
The name Thara is beautiful too.
But besides just your name.
I want to get to know you much better.
Can you promise me.
That once we leave this place.
We'll still be friends.
Do you really want us to be just friends?
Despite the toughness of this training,
You have all made it through with grace.
I am very pleased.
I am both happy and proud.
To have female police officers,
who are as capable and high-quality
as all of you, serving as a vital force.
Another matter for today.
We are honored
By the presence of Police General
Phakphum Ratchanon.
Deputy Commissioner
General of the Royal Thai Police,
To give a speech.
And to present certificates
to each and every one of you.
All rise.
Salute the commanding officer.
Stand tall.
Please be seated.
First of all,
I would like to congratulate all of you,
on completing the training,
and graduating today.
V.I.P. protection,
is not just about physical ability alone.
But we must use our intellect,
instinct,
spirit,
and your heart,
alongside one another.
I hope that
you will never forget this training.
And use what you've learned
to protect people
to the best of your abilities
and with true professionalism.
I would like
to share a little something personal.
Today,
my daughter
is here as well.
Her code is 021.
Phavika Ratchanon.
If, during the training
my daughter
has done anything to cause you trouble,
or made things difficult for you,
I sincerely apologize for that.
Today, I'll allow everyone
to complain about her.
You can criticize her,
but please, don't be too harsh.
This Saturday is my daughter's birthday.
We're having a small celebration.
Please bring Looknam along.
The kids can be friends.
Looknam, please come, dear.
You don't need to bring any gifts, dear.
Just coming to play with her is enough.
Yes.
- Hello.
- Oh.
Hello.
- Hello. Hello.
- Hello.
Happy birthday, little one.
Thank you.
Go leave the gift with your mom first.
Then, take P'Looknam inside
to have some snacks.
- Yes.
- Please.
- Mom.
- Huh.
P’Looknam brought me a gift
and so did the other friends.
Ok.
Wow.
your name is Looknam?
Yes.
Hmm.
Cute.
The name really suits the owner.
Thank you.
See?
Her name is quite Thai.
It’s actually very cute.
But Nong Noo sounds so old-fashioned.
It's old-fashioned.
Thank you for coming, dear.
Yes.
Happy birthday day to you
Happy birthday day, Happy birthday day.
Go ahead, blow it!
Oh.
Yay.
Be a good girl for your mom, okay?
I wish you so much happiness, dear.
- So, shall we start opening the gifts now?
- Let's do it!
Hurry up.
- Open mine first, Open mine.
- Open mine.
This one.
- Huh?
A pencil case.
- It’s as cute as you are.
- And it's pink, too.
Do you like it?
- I love it.
- Hmm.
- Which one? Which one?
- This one is mine!
Which one would you like, Nong Noo?
- Take your pick.
- Let's go with this one first.
Whoa!
A storybook.
An English storybook, too.
The title is Frog and Toad.
This one is mine.
- Umm.
- Whoa.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Frog and Toad were best friends.
One day...
Toad was sitting in front of his house.
He looked very sad.
He said,
No one
has ever written him a letter.
Frog heard this,
so he rushed back home.
He took out a piece of paper and wrote.
Dear Toad,
You are my very best friend.
I am happy that you are in my life.
After that,
Frog
Went to find the mail bird.
and said,
Please deliver this to Toad.
I want to got a letter too.
I'll send you one myself.
Smile for the camera, dear!
How was the training?
It's quite tough, sir.
And how about my daughter?
She was great, sir.
Sir.
Thank you very much
for being here today, sir.
Excuse me.
Daddy.
I miss you.
How are you?
Are you doing well?
- Ok.
- Ok?
What happened to your hand?
Just a minor accident.
But it’s nothing serious.
An accident?
This is a big deal.
Why didn't you tell me.
You and P’X are both the same.
There have been so many times.
That you've tricked me into coming here.
I still haven't settled the score with you yet.
Well...
I didn't want you to worry,
so you could focus on your training.
Look, I'm perfectly fine. I'm still very strong.
Don't you know?
Your dad is made of steel!
Hm.
Dad,
I have someone
I’d like to introduce to you.
Who is it?
Thank you so much for honoring
us with your presence today, sir.
I’ve wanted to meet you
in person for a long time.
021 I mean, Ms. Phavika.
You are very impressive.
I’ve known since the first day
that you were something special.
The apple really doesn't fall far from the tree.
In that case,
let’s exchange Line contacts, shall we?
Sure.
May we please take a photo with you, sir?
Sure thing, come on in!
Please excuse me for a moment.
I’ll go fetch my friends first.
May I
Oh, sure.
Hello, Vicky.
Congratulations!
We...
Do we know each other?
I'm Bawornthat,
Minister Burin's son.
I used to have black hair,
but I'm looking a bit too cool now,
so it’s red.
Ah, Minister Burin.
Congratulations.
How was your day? Are you tired?
Well...
It was quite tiring.
Wow.
My son just came back
from abroad earlier this year.
I'd like him to get to know your daughter.
If the two of them like each other.
That would be wonderful.
By the way.
Do you like flowers?
What exactly are you doing?
Well, I’m just here for the party meeting.
When my daughter opened her shop.
You already meddled once.
- And now, you’ve brought your son here yourself.
- Please excuse me.
Umm.
Don't be so cynical.
I was just showing some kindness.
I know
you're threatening me.
This is exactly why I suggested
that our families join together.
If we were on the same side,
I would have no reason to threaten you.
I can’t be on the same side as
someone who tried to have me killed.
But didn't we used to be on the same side?
You know exactly why that changed.
Stop using your old tactics.
I know
that the opposition is coming after you.
If you don't want to end up in prison
sooner than you should.
Stay away from my daughter.
I'm Vicky.
My real name is Phavika.
That's a very beautiful name.
Her code is 021.
Phavika Ratchanon.
Hey, she's here.
Wait.
Why are you alone?
Yeah.
Wasn't 021 supposed to come back with us?
She’s inside.
I guess she's going back with her dad.
Let's go.
Tarn.
- Tarn.
- Wait.
What's wrong.
Huh?
Is 021 really Deputy
Commissioner Phakphum’s daughter?
Wait.
Are you two hiding something from me?
Look, it's like this.
Deputy Phakphum is the Deputy Chief of Police,
and Tarn doesn't really get along with him.
But somehow, she still wants to work for him.
That's all I know.
Tarn.
What's going on?
Talk to me.
I’ve told you guys before, right?
That my dad fell to his death.
My mom and I believe
that it wasn't a suicide.
Why did you do this?
- Sir, Mr. Wikarn fell and died at the scene.
- Who is going to take care of our child?
We're processing
evidence to find the cause, sir.
Mrs.
please calm down. Stay calm.
Phi.
Twenty years ago,
My father was threatened by a capitalist
to sell our shophouses at a cheap price.
The villagers were terrified,
so they all gave in and sold their places.
But my father refused.
He became the leader,
fighting back against that capitalist.
He gathered all the evidence and went to the police.
The officer in charge of the case back then
was Inspector Phakphum Ratchanon.
My father was in contact with him
for nearly a year.
It seemed like he was on my father's side.
But for some reason, my father ended up dead.
Inspector, sir.
Could you please tell me a bit
more about what happened that day?
I went to see him at his house that day,
around 3 PM.
From our conversation,
he seemed extremely stressed.
He was talking in circles.
It didn't make much sense.
Maybe... well,
he was stressed.
I could really feel how overwhelmed he was.
And then what?
He told me he couldn't take it anymore.
He didn't want to fight anymore.
He said if anything happened to him,
to please look after his wife and child.
The police concluded that
my father committed suicide.
But no matter what, my mom refuses
to believe he would ever abandon us.
My dad wasn't that kind of person
One of the reasons
I became a cop was because of this.
I want to know what really happened,
and I've been waiting for the moment to face him.
But it's freaking dangerous, Tarn.
He’s risen so high now.
There’s no way you can take him down.
If I were your father,
I wouldn't want you to
risk your life and your future.
For a truth that might not even be provable.
So you guys are just going
to leave me wondering like this?
Even if I can't get revenge,
I still need to know.
But he's 021’s father!
Umm.
Now that you know this,
does it make things harder
or easier?
Is she asleep?
Or she is working?
It seems like you
really like this friend of yours.
She's a very kind person.
And she's very gentle, too.
But when something serious,
she’s incredibly precise.
Just like you, Dad.
Sometimes, I even think.
That she should be your child instead of me.
Is that so?
And what’s his name?
Tara.
Captain Tarn.
She's the one who helped me
at the shop that day.
It’s unbelievable.
It's like fate is playing a joke on us.
Crazy coincidence.
Where are you going?
Hanging out, Pa.
Do you expect me to just wither away at home?
Did you go see Phakphum's daughter yet?
Already did, Pa.
She’s not even that pretty.
And she’s not really my type.
Don't tell me.
You prefer that old doctor lady.
Women like the ones you prefer
are hard to control.
Find someone submissive.
They're much easier to control.
I don’t care who you sleep with.
But if you can make Vicky fall for you,
it’ll be to my advantage.
You know very well
that I’m in a tight spot right now.
If that guy Phakphum leaks
the evidence to the opposition.
We’re screwed.
Pa.
Just get rid of him, Pa.
Like you did with the others.
He won't be lucky enough
to survive every time.
Thank you.
Hey, Pete.
You have to stop Tarn from
working with that Deputy, you hear me?
You've got to make it happen.
You know what.
Pete, I gotta go. Talk later!
P'Ann.
Are you alright?
I’m just feeling a bit dizzy.
I guess I haven’t had enough sleep.
Are you sure you’re okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Careful. Take a seat, slowly.
Don’t get so caught up with
patients that you forget yourself.
I've been clearing my schedule lately.
I'm thinking of taking a break
and going abroad for a while.
Hey.
Or...
Is there a surprise proposal?
Don't be silly.
I'm still very much single.
Wait.
Then...
Who’s that guy?
The one with the glam look?
You know,
the one you went out to dinner with last week.
Noey.
Don't tell anyone about this yet.
It’s not official yet.
Got it!
I have a favor to ask you.
It won't interfere with your main duties.
During your days off,
I'd like you to help provide some security.
No problem at all, sir.
I haven't even told you yet
who you'll be looking after.
Isn't it you, sir?
It's my daughter.
Vicky.
Ever since that night,
I've been very worried about her.
The reason I sent Vicky for training
was so she could learn to defend herself.
But if someone was there to look after her.
I'd feel much better.
She trusts you.
And I trust you.
I've received the package, P'Mart.
Oh.
It’s been changed to the meeting room
on the third floor?
Which building?
I see.
Building Three.
If I may speak frankly,
I don't want to spend my off-time carrying bags
for some high-society while she's shopping.
I thought you knew my daughter well enough
not to say something like that.
Fine.
I’ll take that as a refusal.
Okay. I'll do it.
Hey, stop.
Hey.
Mr. Bawornthat.
Captain Tarn.
I was just going to help Vicky carry her things.
Do you two know each other?
This is Mr. Bawornthat.
Minister Burin’s son.
And this
Captain Tarn.
A friend of mine
Pleasure to meet you, Captain Tarn.
Hello.
I'm sorry, I misunderstood the situation.
I happened to have a meeting nearby,
so I thought I’d ask Vicky out for lunch.
I’m afraid that’s not possible.
It’s almost 1 PM already.
She's right.
I have another meeting soon,
and I need to deliver these items
to my seniors.
I see.
That's fine.
Maybe next time then.
I hope I'll have the honor of your company, Vicky.
And Captain Tarn.
I'm sorry if I startled you earlier.
We'll be taking our leave now.
Let's go.
Captain Tarn.
Why haven’t you been answering my calls?
I was actually planning to go
and wait for you at your office.
I've been really busy with work.
Still,
don't overwork yourself.
I'm worried.
You're the one who’s more concerned.
You're on the phone without
looking at your surroundings.
What if someone with bad
intentions was actually following you?
Hey, you...
Hey!
Ouch!
Ever since that night at Vicky’s shop.
I’ve been very worried about her.
I’d like you to help provide some security
I thought you said you were
going to stop seeing that rich girl.
I've given it some thought.
Being a bodyguard for anyone
is the same thing,
As long as I can get into that house
to find evidence, that's enough.
Don't be so stubborn.
I know you too well, Tarn.
You’re worried about her.
I know what happened
at the Royal Thai Police HQ today.
And I know exactly what you know,
That this was likely no accident.
If you're going because your heart tells you to,
then I'm with you.
But if you're going because
of Deputy Phakphum,
then I’m against it.
Because if Vicky ever finds out the truth,
She’ll think you’ve just been using her as a tool.
But I’ve had this in mind
since long before I knew her.
She wasn't the reason I started this.
And do you think she’ll understand that, Tarn?
You have to make a choice.
Whether you're going to keep investigating,
Or choose Vicky,
And just let the past go.
Why does she have to be his daughter?
So, this is Captain Tarn.
Oh, wow.
Who would've thought she’d be this beautiful?
Huh?
What?
And who exactly is she protecting?
Huh?
Vicky?
(All eyes on Bawornthat & Vicky: Political)
(and Police heirs—the next power couple)
Vicky.
Who is Vicky?
Oh.
She is...
Is...
Are you talking business with a foreigner?
Oh.
Yeah, a foreign client
You’re such a hard worker.
You never stop working.
So diligent.
Come on,
the folks in Europe are in a hurry.
I miss you so much.
Hold on, hold on.
And about what you said
taking me on a trip to Europe
when should we go?
Look,
I'm really busy lately.
Aren't you busy yourself?
By the way,
when did you reschedule
Deputy Phakphum’s surgery to?
Hmm.
I'm still looking for a date.
Here comes.
Here is the cake.
Captain Tarn.
It really is Captain Tarn.
Wow.
You’re so beautiful in person.
stunning!
Plus.
You're so cool, too.
I’m not dreaming, am I?
Vicky, please tell me I'm not.
Uh...
I mean, I’m such a huge fan of yours,
May I take a photo with you?
Please?
Sure.
Thank you.
A selfie is fine too.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Let me see the photo for sec.
No, no, it's not very good.
Um, Vicky, could you take a photo for me?
Make it a good one, okay?
Please.
Fine.
Thank you.
Uh...
A normal pose is fine.
One, two, three.
Oh, can we do a heart pose too?
- Heart?
- Yes.
Yes.
One, two, three.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Wow.
The photos are so beautiful!
I can finally rest in peace tonight.
Mali.
She is a huge fan of the Captain.
I guess it's time
to change your phone's wallpaper.
Let's go.
Uh...
Wait a moment.
Uh.
Did you say you didn't know Captain Tarn?
Why are you two together today?
Uh.
Well...
We met during the training.
Now we are...
Friend.
It’s because of my dad.
After what happened at the shop last time,
He’s been incredibly worried about me.
So he assigned the Captain to look after me,
Just for peace of mind.
I feel safe now, too!
Captain Tarn, you can come here every day.
Even on the days Vicky doesn't come.
You can still come by.
I’d just be in the way.
I'm not sure how much help I’d be.
Not at all!
Just standing there looking cool like this
makes the customers feel safe.
Take it down.
Won't there be trouble having
the famous Captain Tarn as my subordinate?
I’m more afraid that
I’ll be the one to mess things up.
If you mess anything up,
I’m reporting you to the Department!
Take off your shirt.
Take it off.
To bake.
Weren't you going to help me?
Oh.
Yes.
Over there.
Put on your apron.
Turn around.
Captain Tarn...
You actually have a pretty great figure.
In this look...
You're so cute it hurts.
Silly girl.
Oh.
So, is there anything I can help you with?
I should fold these boxes, right?
I told you not to stare.
But I want to.
What are you gonna do about it?
A good police must be
an enemy of bad people.
If you're a bad cop,
you're an enemy of good people.
I thought you said you
were done with that young lady.
The statute of limitations for that
case will expire in a few months.
If I let it slide,
Burin won't have
to take any responsibility at all?
I heard...
You’ve become a bodyguard for Vicky?